http://northstar.church/legal/

Skip to contentPanama CityPanama City BeachCallawayStart a CampusLocationsHelping the Whole World Find and Follow JesusI’m NewOur PastorOur TeamOur StoryWhat We BelieveVisitLocationsPanama City CampusPanama City Beach CampusCallaway CampusMinistriesKidsStudentsSmall GroupsCare & CounselingDream TeamYes!Watch OnlineGivePrayerLegalPrivacy PolicyWe know that you care how information about you is used and shared. We hope the following statements will help you understand how we will collect, use and protect the information you provide to us on our site. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.a. We use the personal information that you submit to operate, maintain and provide you the features and functionality of this website and support the vision of Northstar Church. All personal information provided to Northstar Church will only be used internally for ministry purposes.b. We will never share, rent or sell your personal information without your permission unless required to do so by law or by subpoena. We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data.c. We process personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.d. Northstar Church may contain optional links to partners and third party Internet sites and services that may collect data from you or your computer. Please be aware that if you choose to leave our site via a link, Northstar Church assumes no responsibility for the privacy practices or the content of other websites.Media ReleaseNorthstar Church reserves the right to use any photograph/video taken at any event sponsored by Northstar, without the expressed written permission of those included within the photograph/video. Northstar may use the photograph/video in publications or other media material produced, used or contracted by Northstar including but not limited to: brochures, invitations, books, newspapers, magazines, television, websites, etc.To ensure the privacy of individuals and children, images will not be identified using full names or personal identifying information without written approval from the photographed subject, parent or legal guardianA person attending a Northstar event who does not wish to have their image recorded for distribution should make their wishes known to the photographer, and/or the event organizers, and/or contact Northstar at 430 W 5th Street, Suite 400 Panama City, FL 32401, in writing of his/her intentions and include a photograph. Northstar will use the photo for identification purposes and will hold it in confidence.By participating in a Northstar event or by failing to notify Northstar, in writing, your desire to not have your photograph used by Northstar, you are agreeing to release, defend, hold harmless and indemnify Northstar from any and all claims involving the use of your picture or likeness.Any person or organization not affiliated with Northstar may not use, copy, alter or modify Northstar photographs, graphics, videography or other, similar reproductions or recordings without the advance written permission of an authorized designee from Northstar.
Go to Top
